Balikpapan, .. October 2012

To:

# **Human Resources Department**

Dear Sir/Madame,

I am a graduate from vocational high schools in the Department of Informatics Engineering at BALIKPAPAN - East Kalimantan in 2006 and had undergone lectures at the University majoring in Samarinda Mulawarman S-1 SCIENCE STATISTICS. Today I joined in a company engaged in the field of Computer Repair and Maintanance and Printer - SUSECOM (SOURCE COMPUTER SERVICE) I served as TECHNICIAN and programmers. I can operate the computers especially Ms. Word, Ms Excel, Ms. Acces.

I am healthy, ready to work hard, Obviously I have a high motivation and loyalty, be sure to adjust to the work environment, able to complete the tasks that will be given in detail, for which I am prepared to join and contribute to develop the potential of the company of which Mr / Mrs lead, and I'm ready to be placed in all existing work area.

I enclosed the latest Pas Photo, photo copy of ID card, copy of last diploma, Copy of certificates and curriculum vitae indicating my resume and experience

My hope Mr / Ms can consider. and if further information is needed, I am willing to at interview and a test. For attention and the opportunity you gave me thank you.

Sincerely yours,

Mahathir Muhammad, S.Si.

#### DAFTAR RIWAYAT HIDUP/CURICULUM VITAE



### **Personal Data**

Name : Mahathir Muhammad, S.Si.

Place, Date of Birth : Bontang, 30 Maret 1989

**Region** : Islam

Address : Jln. Bonto Bolaeng No 68 RT 1 Kelurahan Sumber

Rejo Balikpapan – EAST KALIMANTAN

**Phone** : (0542) 7020806 / 085247180006

E-mail : mahathir.stat06@gmail.com

# **Education Background**

a. Year 2006 - 2012 : S1 Statistical Science/ Faculty of Mathematics and

Natural Sciences, in Mulawarman University

Samarinda

b. Year 2003 - 2006 : Majoring in Information Technology and

Communications Vocational High School in SMK

Negeri 1 Balikpapan

c. Year 2000 - 2003 : Junior High School in SMP Negeri 6 Balikpapan

d. Year 1994 - 2000 : Primary School in SD Negeri 057 Balikpapan

#### **Skills**

### Skills include the following:

- Statistics
- Hardware and Software maintanance.
- Computer Programming (Visual Basic, Delphi, Pascal).
- Microsoft Office (Microsof Word, Excel, Power Point).
- Microsoft Visio.
- Application Statistics (SPSS, Maple, Matlab)
- The application of the Internet.

### **Work Experience**

- Technicians at CV. Sumber Service Year 2011 till now
- Assistant Laboratory Computational Statistics Year 2007 to 2010
- Trainer Ms. Office in the Institute courses Technocrat College Dublin in March 2011 to December 2011
- Partners Bank Indonesia East Kalimantan as a Research Team Year 2011 to 2012
- Partner Badan Pusat Statistik of East Kalimantan as Surveyor of the Year 2009 to 2010
- Maintanance Computer and Networking in English languange Centre Samarinda Year 2008 to 2011
- Research Team Research Institution "Central Social Marketing Post" / CSPM Year 2006 to 2010

### **Organization**

- Head of Senior Secondary Level 1 Band Festival East Kalimantan cooperation between "Keluarga Pelajar Mahasiswa/ i Balikpapan" (KPMB) with "Badan Narkotika Provinsi" East Kalimantan in 2010
- Competition Committee Chairman Lovely Walk Balikpapan Mayor Cup in 2009
- Head of the Department of Social and Community Chaplaincy KPMB in Samarinda Year 2008-2009
- Members of Student Executive Board (BEM) Faculty Unmul Year 2007-2008

- Head of the Department of Data and Information Propagation Institute
  Campus Al-Hikmah Year 2007-2008
- Head of the Department of Community Services Student Association Statistics
  Year 2007-2008
- Secretary hostel Son Balikpapan Year 2006-2007
- KPMB Anniversary Committe:
  - 1. Jalan Santai Bebas Narkoba 2007
  - 2. Asmaba X-Tra 2008
  - 3. Lomba Gerak Jalan Indah 2009
  - 4. The Senior High Band Festival as East kalimantan BNP Cup in 2010
  - 5. Jalan Santai 1000 Tangan KPMB 2011
  - 6. Futsal as high school level East Kalimantan 2012
- Commite "Bimbingan Belajar dan Try Out SNMPTN KPMB Year 2007 until 2011

## **Course / Training Record**

• September, 31 2012 : Training Package Computer Program Statistics R

• May – June 2008 : ELC english Course

• June – July 2011 : English Course at English First

• March 2010 : Counting BPS Officer Training Kaltim

• 15 May 2009 : Microsoft Office Training

• 3 January 2005 : Course Applications Milcrosoft Excel

• 10 January 2004 : Course Applications Microsoft Word

Curriculum Vitae I created this in good faith and be accountable.

Sincerely yours,,

Mahathir Muhammad S.Si